export const QuizData=[
    {
        question: " How to get a response from an activity in Android?",
        options:["startActivityToResult()","startActiivtyForResult()","Bundle()","None"],
        answer: 2  
    },
    {
        question:"What is the use of the $inc operator in MongoDB?",
        options:["To increment the value of a field by a specified amount","To insert a new document into a collection","To remove a field from a document","None"],
        answer:1

    },
    {
        question:"What command is used to start the React local development server?",
        options:["npm build","npm run dev","npm serve","npm start"],
        answer:2
    },
    
    {
        question:" what will be the output of the code snippet print(NaN==NaN);",
        options:["true","undefined","Error","false"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question:" How is it possible to create chainable route handlers for a route path in Express.js?",
        options:["Using app.routes()","Using app.routing()","Using app.route()","Using app.router()"],
        answer:3

    },
    {
        question:"By default, npm installs any dependency in the global mode",
        options:["true","false"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"If a component is in the ../myComps/ folder instead of being in the ../components/ folder, can it be used?",
        options:["No a Component not found error will be thrown","Yes the name of the folder does not matter " , "No a myComps is an invalid directory error will be thrown","No,a Component needs to be in the components directory error will be thrown"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Why 'next/link' is used in NextJS?",
        options:["image processing","text formatting","navigations to another routes","None of these"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
      question:"what is the o/p of var a=true+true+true*3 print(a)",
      options:["3","0","error","5"],
      answer:4
    },
    {
        question:"How many Orientations does android support?",
        options:["10","11","4","2"],
        answer:3
    },
];